Ah! I like where this is headed.
"Your task is to rescue their leader
from a dungeon of ogres."
(Sheldon:)That's a saucy twist.
"That leader's name: Santa Claus."
(Sheldon:)No, no, no.
It's actually "ho, ho, ho,"
but you'll get the hang of it.
(Leonard:)Thought it'd be fun to make
a holiday-themed quest.
Fun? Mixing Dungeons & Dragons
with Christmas...
(Sheldon:)...is like making a sandwich of grape jelly,
the best-tasting jelly...
(Sheldon:)...and petroleum jelly,
the worst-tasting jelly.
(Leonard:)Okay, here we go.
"You find yourselves in the smoking
remains of Santa's village.
Clearly a great battle has taken place."
(Raj:)Oh, man, the first monster I see,
I'm going to sneak up behind him...
(Raj:)...whip out my wand
and shoot my magic all over his ass.
(Stuart:)Do you hear yourself
when you say these things?
(Leonard:)Okay, there are ogre tracks and
a trail of broken candy canes in the snow.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, what do you do?
(Sheldon:)I signal my contempt for your cruel plan
to shove Christmas joy down my throat...